<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Paul&#39;s Garden</title>
    <link>https://garden.pcarleton.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Paul&#39;s Garden</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 06:40:26 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://garden.pcarleton.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Orbits</title>
      <link>https://garden.pcarleton.com/post/orbits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 06:40:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://garden.pcarleton.com/post/orbits/</guid>
      <description>I have a bizarre way of playing Kerbal Space Program. I&amp;rsquo;ve done it at least three times. I go to a YouTube series by CheersKevin called &amp;ldquo;Kerbal Space Programming&amp;rdquo;. I watch the episodes, and play along. I get to about episode #3 or #4, and somewhere along the way, I get deep into a rabbit hole with the math and optimization available. I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;ve ever made it to the episode where he lands on the &amp;ldquo;Mun&amp;rdquo; (the Moon equivalent of KSP).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ludum Dare</title>
      <link>https://garden.pcarleton.com/post/ludum-dare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 07:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://garden.pcarleton.com/post/ludum-dare/</guid>
      <description>Two weeks ago was the Game Jam &amp;ldquo;Ludum Dare&amp;rdquo;. I had heard about it for a few years running (this was the 50th instance of it), but had never gotten my act together to actually participate. The gist is a 48 hour period where you create a game from start to finish: all graphics, concepts, code, music etc. You can be pretty intense about it and not sleep a lot, or you can be like me and forget about it until partway through Saturday, then spend a couple hours on Sunday hurriedly throwing something together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notebook CSS</title>
      <link>https://garden.pcarleton.com/post/notebook-css/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 20:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://garden.pcarleton.com/post/notebook-css/</guid>
      <description>What if I wanted this page to look like a notebook? Like with the dots like I had in e-notes (TODO make a shortcode for doign this: https://gohugo.io/templates/shortcode-templates/)
I can do it for sure, I guess the question is whether it actually looks good. One of the issues is that it&amp;rsquo;s not really lined up with the written text.
 .main { background-image: radial-gradient(#212121 5%, #fdfdfd 6%); background-position: 0 7px; background-size: 15px 15px; height: 10px; width: 100%; }  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Electronic Notes</title>
      <link>https://garden.pcarleton.com/post/e-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 08:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://garden.pcarleton.com/post/e-notes/</guid>
      <description>As I was reading a bunch of the Economist (TODO: figure out how to link easily between articles&amp;hellip;), I started keeping notes in logseq (TODO: also link there, I think I wrote something?). And I used some spaced-repitition to remember the facts (inconsistently to be honest, but I got some usage out of it. I can now remember reliably the new prime minister of Bulgaria (although I forgot it when I was chatting about it with a co-worker recently)).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Metrics</title>
      <link>https://garden.pcarleton.com/post/metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 07:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://garden.pcarleton.com/post/metrics/</guid>
      <description>I want to get a pageview counter going, but I&amp;rsquo;m kind of into the &amp;ldquo;no Google Analytics trend&amp;rdquo; (fun fact, I used to work on Google Analytics!) I mostly just absolutely hate the &amp;ldquo;Cookie&amp;rdquo; prompt, and while I don&amp;rsquo;t think anybody would come after me for forgetting to put a prompt on, I&amp;rsquo;d like to try getting some metrics where I host it on my own domain.
One option would be to not get metrics, and just write for the fun of it, not caring if anybody sees it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git pre-commit for Hugo</title>
      <link>https://garden.pcarleton.com/post/hugo-pre-commit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 20:12:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://garden.pcarleton.com/post/hugo-pre-commit/</guid>
      <description>I want to build my site on commit, here&amp;rsquo;s what I tried first:
set -eux rm -rf public hugo git add public echo &amp;quot;updated build directory&amp;quot; This worked! But it took some fiddling because I mistakenly set the date of this post in the future. Apparently you can do that and Hugo won&amp;rsquo;t add the pages for it, so it was running the build command but not actually updating anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo</title>
      <link>https://garden.pcarleton.com/post/hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 20:13:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://garden.pcarleton.com/post/hugo/</guid>
      <description>Switching ports fixed a connection problem for some reason&amp;hellip;
  the default one through sudo apt-get install hugo was from 2020, so intalled from source instead.
  Render: doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to be picking up my commits as pulls.
 Just kidding it worked this time.    All my links are to &amp;ldquo;example.com&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; uhoh. Maybe I need to re-install the theme?
 Problem was the &amp;ldquo;baseUrl&amp;rdquo; in the config.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden Fun</title>
      <link>https://garden.pcarleton.com/post/garden-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 10:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://garden.pcarleton.com/post/garden-fun/</guid>
      <description>A list of fun things I want to play around with on this:
 A favicon that has the moon but adjusts with the phase Similarly, but on the top of the page Some kind of counter that says how long its been since I posted, maybe some kind of &amp;ldquo;staleness&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; could be an encouragement to write more or an indicator that it&amp;rsquo;s time to delete some things Generally messing with &amp;ldquo;themes&amp;rdquo; to personalize it more (there&amp;rsquo;s 3 different &amp;ldquo;modes&amp;rdquo; of PaperMod) Trying to make the [[post title]] style links from Logseq work here  Emoji favicon https://css-tricks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Economist odds and ends</title>
      <link>https://garden.pcarleton.com/post/economist/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 20:29:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://garden.pcarleton.com/post/economist/</guid>
      <description>I got a subscription to the Economist for Christmas this year (Thanks Taylor!). I&amp;rsquo;ve tried to read the whole thing cover to cover each week, but I&amp;rsquo;ve never been close to being up to speed (Currently a full issue plus some behind). That goal came from this tweet:
I read @TheEconomist cover-to-cover because its content makes me think critically about the world. Its editors recently asked me a tough question: What is the one thing you&amp;#39;d do to create a more open world?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Render</title>
      <link>https://garden.pcarleton.com/post/render/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 20:51:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://garden.pcarleton.com/post/render/</guid>
      <description>Render.com Register (with Github) a. (Act on your behalf): looks like it will only be able to do that on resources I grant the app access to New Static Site Push this thing to Github a. looks like it needs to be public, but I guess that&amp;rsquo;s the point anyway i. This got me thinking about how my github might actually get more traffic from people I know versus my blog which is exclusively strangers afaict.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden</title>
      <link>https://garden.pcarleton.com/post/garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 20:13:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://garden.pcarleton.com/post/garden/</guid>
      <description>Gardening I read a few posts awhile back (I&amp;rsquo;ll link to them at some point, Will Larson) about a digital garden. Something that&amp;rsquo;s a little messy, your little corner of the internet. It&amp;rsquo;s not fully edited, it&amp;rsquo;s not trying to be anything.
That&amp;rsquo;s something I liked. That it&amp;rsquo;s mostly for me, but I can keep iterating on it.
https://joelhooks.com/digital-garden
https://lethain.com/exuberant-sketches/
https://tomcritchlow.com/2019/02/17/building-digital-garden/
Nesting One of the things I found compelling this week was building a floorplan of the apartment I&amp;rsquo;m renting with my partner.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
